paypal-prepaid.com 2014-07-05

# FACTS

                             Your prepaid debit card account is issued and operated by The Bancorp
   and is governed by The Bancorp’s privacy practices. The terms of this Privacy Policy only apply to you if you open an
                               account or use our prepaid debit card or related products or services.
                                                                                                                               Rev 11/2013
                           WHAT DOES THE BANCORP DO
  FACTS                    WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
                           Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
  Why?                     consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how
                           we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                           understand what we do.
  What?                    The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                           have with us. This information can include:
                                 Social Security number and income
                                 account balances and payment history
                                 credit history and credit scores
                           When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information, as described in
                           this notice.
  How?                     All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                           business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                           customers’ personal information, whether The Bancorp shares your information, and whether you
                           can limit this sharing.
  Reasons we can share your personal information                    Does The Bancorp share?              Can you limit this sharing?
  For our everyday business purposes—
  such as to process your transactions, maintain
                                                                                  Yes                                   No
  your account(s), respond to court orders and legal
  investigations, or report to credit bureaus
  For our marketing purposes—
                                                                                  Yes                                   No
  to offer our products and services to you
  For joint marketing with other financial companies                               No                            We don’t share
  For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                                   No                            We don't share
  information about your transactions and experiences
  For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                                   No                            We don't share
  Information about your creditworthiness
  For nonaffiliates to market to you                                              Yes                                  Yes
  To limit                       Call 1- 877-814-7681 - Please be prepared to provide your card number or Social Security
  our sharing                     Number to identify your account, or
                                 Mail the form below.
                            Please note:
                            If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information [30] days from the date we
                            sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information
                            as described in this notice.
                            However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
 Questions?                Call 1-877-814-7681.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Mail-in Form
                            Mark any/all you want to limit:
                                 Do not share my personal information with nonaffiliates to market their products and
                                  services to me.
                          Name                                                                                       Mail to:
                          Address                                                                                    NetSpend Prepaid
                                                                                                                     Debit Card Program
                                                                                                                     P.O. Box 2136
                          City, State, ZIP
                                                                                                                     Austin, TX
                          Card Number                                                                                 78768-2136

Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?                     This privacy policy is provided by The Bancorp and applies to our
                                                  customers who open or use our prepaid debit card or related products or
                                                  services.
What we do
How does The Bancorp protect my                   To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
personal information?                             and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                                  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                                  and buildings.
                                                  We also limit access to information to those employees for whom access
                                                  is necessary.
How does The Bancorp collect my                   We collect your personal information, for example, when you
personal information?
                                                      open an account or pay your bills
                                                      make deposits or withdrawals from your account
                                                      provide account information or give us your contact information.
                                                  We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                                  bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
                                                  Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                                      sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                                         about your creditworthiness
                                                        affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                                      sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                                  State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                                  limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
What happens when I limit sharing                 Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
for an account I hold jointly with
someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                                        Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                                  financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                                      Our affiliates include financial companies such as The Bancorp Bank
                                                       and Bancorp Card Services Inc.
Nonaffiliates                                     Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                                  financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                                       Nonaffiliates we share with can include online payment companies
                                                       and prepaid card providers.
Joint marketing                                   A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                                  together market financial products or services to you.
                                                      The Bancorp does not jointly market.
Other important information
*California Residents -- In accordance with California law, we will not share information we collect about you with
companies outside of The Bancorp, unless the law allows. For example, we may share information with your consent,
to service your accounts, or to provide rewards or benefits to which you are entitled. We will not share information we
collect about you with our joint marketing partners without your authorization. We will limit sharing around our
companies to the extent required by California law.
*Vermont Residents --- In accordance with Vermont law, we will not share personal financial information about you,
other than transaction experience information, with other Bancorp companies or affiliates, nor will we share any
personal financial information about you with other Bancorp companies for marketing purposes.
* Nevada Residents -- We are providing you this notice pursuant to state law. You may be placed on our internal Do
Not Call List by following the directions in the “To limit our sharing” section. Nevada law requires that we also provide
you with the following contact information: Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General, 555
E. Washington St., Suite 3900, Las Vegas, NV 89101; Phone number- 702.486.3132; email: BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us.
